the number of features being added to a language is going up and that's the reason I'm going
to really call the entire course. Now this is a full-fledged course and that's why it's so lengthy
but you cannot finish the entire course in one day even if it says 12 hours or 13 hours it will
take time. Now let's talk about Java. Now why Java is so famous? Now if you see the programming index
the top 5 programming language you will always find Java there maybe at the first position or at
the fourth position you will find Java. Why Java is so famous is because Java has multiple features
which helps it to be used in the enterprise market. I mean not just enterprise market it can be used
for mobile development web development and of course enterprise application and most of the big
companies if you go there they are using Java as their preferred language. Now in Java we have
a technology called JVM and it's not just Java we have multiple languages running on JVM so even if
you are working on some other languages let's say Kotlin, Scala, Groovy, ultimately you're working
on Java technology and that's why if you learn Kojava it is much easier for you to jump to different
languages and I've also observed irrespective of which interior going.